<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ArrayOfVacancy xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Vacancy Id="7922434" Hot="true">
    <Name>Senior DevOps (Azure) Engineer, IoT platform</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T15:01:00.097</Date>
    <CityName>Днепр</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>Our client is a technology company offering a smart city-focused IoT platform based on oneM2M. The Data Exchange/Marketplace solution enables data ingestion, exposure, and entitlement across third-party data sources and users. The platform acts as a data</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>DataArt</CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7922451" Hot="true">
    <Name>Middle DevOps Engineer, Global Recorded Music Company</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T15:01:00.097</Date>
    <CityName>Днепр</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>Our client is a global music and entertainment industry conglomerate headquartered in the US with offices in over 40 countries. Currently, the company plans to expand the team and run the following projects: processing tools for new artists and tracks,</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>DataArt</CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7842004" Hot="true">
    <Name>Оператор технической поддержки со знанием польского языка</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T14:01:00.54</Date>
    <CityName>Киев</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>Компания Lime Devs в связи с расширением приглашает к сотрудничеству клёвых и ответственных ребят для работы в контакт-центре.Требования к кандидату:Четкая и грамотная речь;Владение польским (выше среднего) , так и русским языками (в письменном и устном</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>Lime Devs</CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7913280" Hot="true">
    <Name>HelpDesk/Junior System Administrator</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T14:01:00.54</Date>
    <CityName>Киев</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>Количество наших приложений стремительно растёт, мы активно расширяем команду и ищем того, кто поможет нашему HelpDesk инженеру осуществлять техническую поддержку офисных и удаленных сотрудников. Ты станешь настоящим супергероем для каждого из нас! Чем</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>Amazing Apps</CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7093002" Hot="true">
    <Name>Intern (Junior developer)</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T13:01:00.14</Date>
    <CityName>Киев</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>Innoware is recognized as experts in the consulting services, specializing in ERP and CRM implementations and cloud business solutions. Our company holds Microsoft Gold Certified Partner status and acknowledged as one of the best partners in Eastern Europe.</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>INNOWARE</CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7887324" Hot="true">
    <Name>BI &amp; DW Developer</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T13:01:00.14</Date>
    <CityName>Киев</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>Teva Ukraine that is a large international pharmaceutical company in Ukraine is looking for an accomplished professional with a wealth of experience in developing, deploying, and maintaining BI interfaces. Office location:Kyiv, 1-V Pavla Tychyny Av.,</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>TEVA</CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7905820" Hot="true">
    <Name>Бізнес-аналітик 1С</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T12:01:00.593</Date>
    <CityName>Киев</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>Ми пропонуємо:зарплата вище ринкової: обговорюється на співбесіді;адекватне завантаження - точний план роботи на 40-годинний робочий тиждень;офіс у центрі (Малевича, 86 Н) - зручно добиратися з усіх районів Києва;фінансова стабільність - офіційне працевлаштування</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>bodo</CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7922376" Hot="true">
    <Name>Інженер-програміст</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T12:01:00.593</Date>
    <CityName>Киев</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>Шановні друзі! Компанія "Охоронний Холдінг" відкрила вакансію в м.Київ "Інженер-програміст" Ми пропонуємо:графік роботи - 9:00 - 18:00 (повна зайнятість);робота в холдинговій компанії (Дніпровський район, массив Воскресенка, орієнтир - «Епіцентр»);охорона</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>Охоронний Холдінг, ТОВ</CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7922238" Hot="true">
    <Name>Customer Support Manager</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T12:01:00.593</Date>
    <CityName>Киев</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>ARVI VR - инновационная компания, которая создает игры для виртуальной реальности. Мы входим в ТОП-3 разработчиков в мире. 30% наших клиентов из Америки - это порядка 100 клиентов. Сейчас у нас 7 игр, и еще 12 запустим в 2020 году. Мы ведем переговоры</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>Сохина А.В., ФЛП</CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7911511" Hot="true">
    <Name>Sales Development Representative (SDR)</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T12:01:00.593</Date>
    <CityName>Киев</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>About LimTC © Limitless Technology Consultants LLC :We're a leading Ukrainian out-staffing company that works with international companies on a long-term basis. LimTC can go from client pain point identification to solution roadmap, on to building out</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>LimTc</CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7881309" Hot="true">
    <Name>Team Lead - Senior Front-End Web Developer (React.Js)</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T12:01:00.593</Date>
    <CityName>Киев</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>HEADWAY is a leading network company which is operating on the US and western Europe . We are a product IT-company designing our own product from the main business. We are experts in the field we've been working in for more than six years! With us, you'll</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>HEADWAY</CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7871440" Hot="true">
    <Name>Middle /Senior JavaScript developer</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T11:01:00.523</Date>
    <CityName>Харьков</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>The Front end Engineer role will be working with modern UI frameworks such as React to deliver UI components for support of the In Home Services line of business. This role will be focused on adding additional features as well as building new front-ends</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>Dish Ukraine</CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7922114" Hot="true">
    <Name>Програмист 1С</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T11:01:00.523</Date>
    <CityName>Одесса</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>Программист 1С ТребованияПрофильное образованиеОпыт работы администрирования учетной программы «1С:Предприятие»Коммуникабельность, исполнительность. ответственность, инициативность.Обязанности:Разработка, внедрение и сопровождение конфигураций;Доработка</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>Bexhill Trading </CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7912795" Hot="true">
    <Name>C++ Developer, Communication Recording Solutions</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T10:01:00.03</Date>
    <CityName>Днепр</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>Our client is a large technology company that develops solutions for recording and working with voice data. Through integration with telephone systems, this open and extensible platform allows to record, manage, and listen to calls live as well as to</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>DataArt</CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7912804" Hot="true">
    <Name>Senior C++ Developer, Financial Management Software</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T10:01:00.03</Date>
    <CityName>Днепр</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>Our client is a leading provider of financial and accounting systems for international enterprises. The company delivers intricate solutions based on Microsoft technologies. DataArt's team is currently supporting the client's existing products and helping</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>DataArt</CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7657127" Hot="true">
    <Name>Тестировщик-аналитик со знаниями управленческого учета</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T09:01:00.477</Date>
    <CityName>Киев</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>Группа компаний «ВЕНБЕСТ» создана в 1991 году и на сегодняшний день является крупнейшей в Украине негосударственной охранной структурой, лидером рынка по комплексной защите объектов различных форм собственности и граждан.В состав группы компаний «ВЕНБЕСТ»</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>ВЕНБЕСТ, ООО </CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7845362" Hot="true">
    <Name>Full-Stack Developer</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T09:01:00.477</Date>
    <CityName>Киев</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>Адрес :с. Петропавловская Борщаговка, ул. Антонова 8а, БЦ "Сенсей" Приглашаем к себе в команду разработчика для работ в веб-программе в сфере финансовых услуг.Команда на этапе стартапа, поэтому первоначально работа будет самостоятельной ( с подключением</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>КошельОК, ТОВ </CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7852060" Hot="true">
    <Name>Аналитик-консультант 1С</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T09:01:00.477</Date>
    <CityName>Днепр</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>Требования:Высшее специализированное (ИТ, Экономика, Бухгалтерия);Навыки работы в 1С:УПП (1С:УТП) на уровне администратора и консультанта;Знания бухгалтерского учета, производственного учета, ЗП и кадров;Знание основ организации проектной работы, навыки</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>Корпорация «Биосфера»</CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7843412" Hot="true">
    <Name>1С Bitrix developer</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T00:01:00.88</Date>
    <CityName>Одесса</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>Крупной развивающейся компании TOTISPHARMA GROUP LTD в связи с расширением требуется опытный 1C Bitrix developer Требования:Опыт в практическом веб-программировании от 3-х лет;Опыт программирования на PHP, MySQL, Javascript;Умение работать с чужим кодом;Опыт</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>Тотисфарма Групп, ООО</CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
  <Vacancy Id="7854187" Hot="true">
    <Name>Системний аналітик</Name>
    <Date>2020-03-14T00:01:00.88</Date>
    <CityName>Киев</CityName>
    <ShortDescription>Очікування від кандидата:Досвід роботи в сфері ІТ не менше 5 років, на позиції системного аналітика не менше 2 роківДосвід коммунікації із замовником для виявлення вимогДосвід формування технічних специфікацій системи на основі бізнес-вимог замовника</ShortDescription>
    <CompanyName>ІТ СПЕЦІАЛІСТ, ТОВ</CompanyName>
  </Vacancy>
</ArrayOfVacancy>